stuffpit.com 2016-11-24

# Privacy Policy

Stuffpit has been set up to enable you to share product recommendations amongst other Stuffpit users. Stuffpit takes great care to protect your personal data and allows you to provide the amount of information that you feel comfortable sharing. By visiting the Stuffpit web site you acknowledge and accept the principles set out in this privacy policy.

This privacy policy covers the treatment of your personal data stored and used by Stuffpit and does not cover the privacy policy of any third parties that are not owned or controlled by Stuffpit.

**Personal Data**  
Stuffpit requires users to register in order to add and share products amongst other users. To do this you will be required to create a profile, store your email address and personal password. Your email address will never be displayed publicly on this website but is required to validate your account and to help you invite and share product recommendations with other users. We ask that your email address exists and is kept up to date.

Registered users choose a username and it is possible to use the site anonymously, it is possible to store other optional information including full name, city, country, gender, date of birth, personal web address and profile. This data may be displayed to other users of Stuffpit.

**Product Data**  
Registered users can add as many products from e-commerce stores online as they wish. These selections will be made available and displayed to all users of the site and associated back to the original user who added the product. This data is displayed to both registered and unregistered users.

**Friends Data**  
As a social networking site, Stuffpit allows unregistered users and non-friends to view any users friends and connections and activity.

**Email Notifications**  
The Social aspect of the Stuffpit web site requires that email notifications are sent to other other registered users and to invite new users. I.e. to invite friends or approve a friend request. We may also notify you of any updates and improvements to the Stuffpit web site. We will not share or disclose the email addresses of our users with any third parties.

**Cookies**  
Cookies are used within the site to store certain options and session information. This includes your country selection, default time span selection and to keep your login session active. Any cookies used do not store, retrieve or transmit any private or personal data.

**Information Security**  
Stuffpit provides users with a password protected account that users must keep private at all times. All data provided to Stuffpit is stored securely in our databases with restricted access to internal staff only. Your data will not be shared with any third parties.
